Guide to the Frank Clyde Brown papers, 1912-1974 RL.00160
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Cylinders and Discs, 10 boxes
  - Wax Cylinders, 1921-1935
    - RL00160-WC-0010, undated (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0010)
      Title: Bill Miller's Trip to the West, performer: Norris, E.J., location: Sands (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:316
      Title: Here Come Three Dukes A-Riding, performer: unknown, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:21:190
    - RL00160-WC-0011, 1921 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0011)
      Title: I Had a Little Ship on the Ocean (Little Sally), performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:28:466
      Title: Ain't Gonna Rain No More, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:445
      Title: Black Eyed Daisy (Send for the Fiddle), performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:229
      Title: As I Went Down to Simon's Mill (Railroad Dinah Gal), performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:38:117
      Title: Skin and Bones (There Was an Old Woman), performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:45:998
      Title: Come All Ye Girls of Adam's Race, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:20:780
      Title: Honey In the Gun, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:401
      Title: Goodbye My Blue Bell, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:29:270
      Title: Everybody Works But Father, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:20:427
      Title: Little Sallie Water, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:022
      Title: Draw a Bucket of Water, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:544
      Title: Animal Song, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:34:154
      Title: Ginger Blue, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:16:015
      Title: Roll Down Dem Bales o' Cotton, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:838
      Title: Went Down Town, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:016
      Title: Sweet Long Ago, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:088
      Title: The Poor Married Man, performer: Mansfield, Mamie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:45:544
    - RL00160-WC-0012, 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0012)
      Title: Workin' On the Railroad Forty Cents a Day, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:763
      Title: The Dummy Line, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:905
      Title: White Gal - Yaller Gal - Black Gal [House text], performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:586
      Title: The Old Grey Mare, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:413
      Title: When a Man Gets the Blues, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:879
      Title: Little Brown Jug, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:509
      Title: Old Molly Hare, performer: Lucas, Louise, location: White Oak (N.C.) | Bladen County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:889
      Title: Kindling Wood (My Name is Dinah), performer: Lucas, Louise, location: White Oak (N.C.) | Bladen County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:789
      Title: Ain't Gonna Worry My Lord No More, performer: Lucas, Louise, location: White Oak (N.C.) | Bladen County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:543
      Title: Farmer Boy, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:118
      Title: unknown, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:18:112
      Title: unknown, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:602
      Title: unknown, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:18:900
      Title: Walk In the Parlor, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:371
      Title: Old Man, Old Man, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:411
      Title: I'm Climbing Up Zion's Hill, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:36:473
      Title: We'll All Pray Together, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:315
      Title: As I Went Down In the Valley, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:244
      Title: Sweat Like Drops of Blood Run Down, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:39:236
      Title: I Have a True Love, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:337
    - RL00160-WC-0013, undated (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0013)
      Title: Isle of St Helena (Boneparte), performer: Grogan, Fannie, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:54:824
      Title: Lord Thomas, performer: Grogan, Fannie, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:18:054
    - RL00160-WC-0014, undated (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0014)
      Title: The Miller and His Three Sons, performer: Tugman, Alexander, location: Todd (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:271
      Title: Poor Married Man, performer: Tugman, Alexander, location: Todd (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:33:791
      Title: Old Soap Gourd [Game], performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:497
      Title: Farmer In the Dell [Game], performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:550
      Title: Down By the Old Mill Stream, performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:101
      Title: When the Bees Are In the Hive, performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:197
      Title: The Needle's Eye, performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:16:102
      Title: The Lover's Lament (Little Molly), performer: Tugman, Alexander, location: Todd (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:229
      Title: Groundhog, performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:074
      Title: Baby Bunting (Bye O Baby Bunting), performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:344
      Title: Frankie and Johnny (Franky Barker), performer: Weaver, Lura, location: Piney Creek (N.C.) | Alleghany County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:854
      Title: Wreck of Old Ninety Seven, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:862
      Title: Lord Thomas and Fair Annet (One Morning InMay), performer: Fincher, Lizzie, location: Monroe (N.C.) | Union County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:620
      Title: Bright Alpharatta, the Indian Girl, performer: Poovey, W.E., location: unknown, running time: 00:01:07:445
    - RL00160-WC-0015, 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0015)
      Title: Captain I'm Driving, performer: White, N.I., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:800
      Title: Put the Dogs On Him, performer: White, N.I., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:586
      Title: Run Here Doctor, performer: White, N.I., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:18:542
      Title: Yonder Come a Yaller Gal, performer: White, N.I., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:602
      Title: Good News Chariots Comin', performer: White, N.I., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:236
      Title: Uncle Bud, performer: Hauchey, H.H., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:209
      Title: O When I Die Don't Bury Me Deep, performer: Hauchey, H.H., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:134
      Title: Did You Ever Go A-Fishing?, performer: Hauchey, H.H., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:963
      Title: It Ain't A Gwine Rain No More, performer: Hauchey, H.H., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:126
      Title: Dig My Grave Deep Wide, performer: Holton, S.M. | Matthews, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:18:597
      Title: unknown, performer: Holton, S.M. | Matthews, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:20:185
      Title: unknown, performer: Holton, S.M. | Matthews, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:16:158
      Title: Nuts in May, performer: Peatross, Edith, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:398
      Title: Who's Gonna Love You, Honey?, performer: Overton, Doris, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:563
      Title: That's Where My Honey Goes, performer: Overton, Doris, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:21:094
      Title: Bye O Baby Bunting, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:300
      Title: London Bridge, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:004
      Title: There Was a Watermelon, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:424
      Title: Whale Swallowed Jonah, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:834
      Title: Possum Up A Simmon Tree, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:400
      Title: A Billy Goat, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:489
      Title: Quitcherter Lookin' Around, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:193
      Title: I Was Born Ten Thousand Years Ago, performer: Mangum, Eura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:24:837
    - RL00160-WC-0016, 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0016)
      Title: Dublin Bay, performer: Cox, Jeannette, location: Winterville (N.C.) | Pitt County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:30:483
      Title: She Gave No Kisses One (Kissing Song), performer: Wright, J.T.C., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:065
      Title: Chewing Gum, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:07:959
      Title: Leather Breeches, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:188
      Title: Just Down to the Gate, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:182
      Title: Jimmie Suttonton, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:370
    - RL00160-WC-0017, 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0017)
      Title: Drifting Apart, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:071
      Title: Shake a Hand, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:288
      Title: Hush, Hush - Mockingbird, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:803
      Title: Let My Name Be Kindly Spoken, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:061
      Title: Poor Old Me Goes Waggin' Along, performer: Belvin, Jennie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:759
      Title: Rise, Shiner, Mourner, performer: Peatross, Edith, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:444
      Title: Raccoon Up a Tree, performer: Peterson, Jessie L., location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:359
      Title: Twenty Years Ago, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:45:573
      Title: Malinda May, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:981
      Title: I Have a Ship On the Ocean, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:37:798
      Title: Down Benath the Diving Bell (Pretty Maggie), performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:701
      Title: That Bloody War, performer: Holton, Aura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:27:804
      Title: Drop O'Dew, performer: Holton, Aura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:34:570
      Title: In a Cool Shady Nook, performer: Holton, Aura, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:11:598
    - RL00160-WC-0018, undated (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0018)
      Title: Red River Valley (Bright Sherman Valley, performer: Hardin, Addie, location: Rutherwood (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:44:369
      Title: Fly Around My Little Miss, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:000
      Title: Twinkle Twinkle Little Star, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:32:907
      Title: Cripple Creek, performer: Moore, Arthur, location: Lenoir (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:11:100
      Title: Will You Love Me When I'm Old, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:842
      Title: Will You Love Me When I'm Old, performer: Greer, I.G., location: Rutherwood (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:389
      Title: Dear Nell, performer: Hardin, Addie, location: Rutherwood (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:647
      Title: My Pretty Quadroon, performer: Greer, I.G., location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:401
      Title: unknown, performer: Hardin, Addie, location: Boone (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:459
      Title: Reuben's Train, performer: Moore, Arthur, location: Lenoir (N.C.) | Caldwell County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:23:904
      Title: Lady Isabeland the Elf Knight, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:119
      Title: In the Shadow of the Pines, performer: McNeill, Hattie, location: Ferguson (N.C.) | Wilkes County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:122
      Title: I'm Determined to Be an Old Maid, performer: Tugman, Alexander, location: unknown, running time: 00:00:22:395
      Title: I'll Put my Knapsack On My Back, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:422
      Title: My Mammy Don't Love Me, performer: Webb, Pearle, location: Pineola (N.C.) | Avery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:21:946
      Title: On the Banks of the Ohio, performer: Hardin, Addie, location: Rutherwood (N.C.) | Watauga County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:548
    - RL00160-WC-0019, circa 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0019)
      Title: Soon as My Foot Struck Zion, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:42:064
      Title: Old Satan's Mad, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:31:438
      Title: John Saw de 144,000, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:25:639
      Title: I Wish I Was Single, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:22:835
      Title: I Got a Gal (or "I Got a Girl"), performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:20:715
      Title: Guinea Negro Song, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:275
      Title: Negro Song, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:785
      Title: Page's Train Runs So Fast, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:630
      Title: Georgia Buck, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:587
      Title: Florence Ran Through the Weevily Wheat, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:528
      Title: Raccoon Has a Bushy Tail, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:101
      Title: Shortnin' Bread, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:858
      Title: Some Folks Say Dat a Nigger Won't Steal, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:26:610
      Title: On the Field of Battle, performer: Robbins, Jewell, location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:49:124
      Title: Johnny Sands, performer: White, N.E., location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:16:368
      Title: Stanin' In the Need of Prayer, performer: White, N.E., location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:39:251
      Title: No Hidin' Place, performer: White, N.E., location: Pekin (N.C.) | Montgomery County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:831
    - RL00160-WC-0020, 1922 (Box 131, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0020)
      Title: Little Mary Fagan (or Phagan), performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:56:786
      Title: The Blind Girl's Death, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:54:348
      Title: Barbara Allen, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:14:948
      Title: Naomi Wise, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:06:066
      Title: George Collins, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:53:737
      Title: Frankie Barker (Frankie and Johnny), performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:08:985
      Title: Leaving the City, Dear Nellie, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:01:346
      Title: Lillian Brown, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:882
      Title: The Farmer Boy, performer: Coleman, Alfonso, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:08:29:950
    - RL00160-WC-0021, 1922 (Box 132, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0021)
      Title: Mama, Mama, Have You Heard, performer: Coleman, Florence, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:19:635
      Title: Mama Sent Me to the Spring, performer: Coleman, Florence, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:346
      Title: Mama Only Loves Her Boy (or Honey), performer: Coleman, Florence, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:51:986
      Title: Little Mohea, performer: Coleman, Florence, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:30:512
      Title: Bobbie Shaftoe, performer: Overton, Doris, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:15:130
      Title: unknown, performer: Overton, Doris | Adams, Monte, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:621
      Title: unknown, performer: Overton, Doris, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:17:107
      Title: unknown, performer: Adams, Monte, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:591
      Title: unknown, performer: Adams, Monte, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:14:796
      Title: unknown, performer: Overton, Doris, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:36:752
      Title: Here Come Three Dukes A-Riding, performer: Overton, Doris, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:10:943
      Title: Twas On a Cold December Day, performer: Coleman, Florence, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:50:134
    - RL00160-WC-0022, circa 1922 (Box 132, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0022)
      Title: I'm Going Over the Rocky Mountains, performer: Mansfield, Mamie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:701
      Title: When I Was Single, performer: Mansfield, Mamie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:12:926
      Title: I Bought a Hen, performer: Mansfield, Mamie, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:02:12:784
      Title: Hungry Bucket, performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:47:173
      Title: I Don't Love Satan, performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:57:608
      Title: Each Evening at Eight, performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:37:550
      Title: River's Up and Still A-Risin', performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:29:936
      Title: I Heard a Mighty Rumblin', performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:31:160
      Title: My Father's a Hedger and A Ditcher, performer: Barbour, Mary, location: Raeford (N.C.) | Hoke County (N.C.), running time: 00:01:00:372
    - RL00160-WC-0023, 1922 (Box 132, Audio-cylinder RL00160-WC-0023)
      Title: Soldier, Soldier Won't You Marry Me, performer: Holeman, Jean, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:46:563
      Title: Captain Jinks of the Horse Marine, performer: Holeman, Jean, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:41:853
      Title: Don't Tell Pa, performer: Holeman, Jean, location: Durham (N.C.) | Durham County (N.C.), running time: 00:00:13:606